Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - P-S
        - P-Funk All-Stars - Urban dancefloor guerillas, 1983; SR-27186; P-Funk All-Stars (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27187. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BFZ 39168; A-side Matrix # AL-39168-1B
          CBS Associated Records
          New York, New York
        - P-Funk All-Stars - Urban dancefloor guerillas, 1983; SR-27187; P-Funk All-Stars (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27186. 2 copies.
        - Pablo - Story of sampling EP, 2001; SR-27188; Pablo (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27189. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RH 003; A-side Matrix # RH-003-A2
          Red Hook Recordings
          Glasgow, United Kingdom
        - Pablo - Story of sampling EP, 2001; SR-27189; Pablo (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27188. 2 copies.
        - Pablo Cruise - Part of the game, 1979; SR-27190; Pablo Cruise (Box 58)
          Catalog # SP 3712; A-side Matrix # SP-03712-A-T3-A+M
          A&M Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - Pacific Gas and Electric - Pacific Gas and Electric, 1969; SR-27191; Pacific Gas and Electric (Box 58)
          Catalog # CS 9900; A-side Matrix # XSM150632-1B
          Columbia
        - Pagan, Bruni - Just Bruni, 1979; SR-27192; Pagan, Bruni (Box 58)
          Catalog # 6E-215; A-side Matrix # 6E-215-A-SP
          Elektra
          Los Angeles, California
        - Pagan, Bruni - Lovers; Late for love, 1979; SR-27193; Pagan, Bruni (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27194. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AS-11438; A-side Matrix # ASS 11438-SP
        - Pagan, Bruni - Lovers; Late for love, 1979; SR-27194; Pagan, Bruni (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27193. 2 copies.
        - Page, Gene - Love starts after dark, 1980; SR-27195; Page, Gene (Box 58)
          Catalog # AB 4262; A-side Matrix # AB 4262-SA-CTH-1
          Arista
        - Page, Gene - Hot city, 1974; SR-27196; Page, Gene (Box 58)
          Catalog # SD 18111; A-side Matrix # STA-743205B
          Atlantic
        - Page, Larry Ork - Skin heat, 1978; SR-27197; Page, Larry Ork (Box 58)
          Catalog # PAGE 2; A-side Matrix # PAGE-2A-1
          Rampage Records
          United Kingdom
        - Palmieri, Eddie - Sentido, 1973; SR-27198; Palmieri, Eddie (Box 58)
          Catalog # MM 103; A-side Matrix # MM103A-1
          Mango
        - Palmieri, Eddie - The sun of Latin music, 1974; SR-27199; Palmieri, Eddie (Box 58)
          Catalog # CLP 109XX; A-side Matrix # CLP 109AXX-1R
          Coco Records
        - Palmieri, Eddie - Gold 1973/1976, 1976; SR-27200; Palmieri, Eddie (Box 58)
          Catalog # CLP 133; A-side Matrix # CLP133
        - Pamplemousse - My love is burning up, 1981; SR-27201; Pamplemousse (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27202. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AVI-6097; A-side Matrix # 091-6097-A
          AVI Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Pamplemousse - My love is burning up, 1981; SR-27202; Pamplemousse (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27201. 2 copies.
        - Panama - Fire, 1978; SR-27203; Panama (Box 58)
          Catalog # PLD 9023; A-side Matrix # PLD-9023-A
          Peters International, Inc.
        - Panarama - Can this be paradise, 1982; SR-27204; Panarama (Box 58)
          Catalog # 6.25179; A-side Matrix # 6.25179-01-1
          Jupiter Records
          Germany
        - Panol, Dominique - Bolotte, 1987; SR-27205; Panol, Dominique (Box 58)
          Catalog # GD 1503; A-side Matrix # GD 1503 A
          GD Productions
          France
        - Paradigm - Get a little freaky, 2001; SR-27206; Paradigm (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27207. Different discs.
          Catalog # ET 15; A-side Matrix # ET-015-A
          F.A.C.T. Records
          Detroit, Michigan
        - I.O.S. - In the mind of Erik?, 1997; SR-27207; I.O.S. (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27206. Different discs.
          Catalog # ET 001; A-side Matrix # ET-001A
        - Paradise Express - Let's fly, 1979; SR-27208; Paradise Express (Box 58)
          Catalog # F-9589; A-side Matrix # F-9589A-
          Fantasy
          Berkeley, California
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - Woman out of control, 1983; SR-27209; Parker, Ray, Jr. (Box 58)
          Catalog # AL 8-8087; A-side Matrix # AL-8-8087-SA -2
        - Parks, Steve - Movin' in the right direction, 1981; SR-27210; Parks, Steve (Box 58)
          Catalog # SS-8012; A-side Matrix # SS 8012-A RE-1
          Solid Smoke
          San Francisco, California
        - Parlet - Play me or trade me, 1980; SR-27211; Parlet (Box 58)
          Catalog # NBLP 7224; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7224-AS PR-1
          Casablanca
        - Parliament - Theme from the black hole; The big bang theory, 1979; SR-27212; Parliament (Box 58)
          Catalog # NBD 20208 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD 20208 AS CR-1
        - Parliament - Aqua boogie (A psychoalphadiscobetabioaquadoloop), 1978; SR-27213; Parliament (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27214. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NBD 20147 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20147-AS P-1
        - Parliament - Aqua boogie (A psychoalphadiscobetabioaquadoloop), 1978; SR-27214; Parliament (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27213. 2 copies.
        - Parliament - Follow the leader, 1995; SR-27215; Parliament; Funkadelic; P-Funk All Stars (Box 58)
          Catalog # 12 HOTH 1; A-side Matrix # 12HOTH 1-A-1-1-
          Hot Hands
        - Parliament - Rhenium, 1990; SR-27216; Parliament (Box 58)
          Catalog # HDH LP 008; A-side Matrix # HDH LP 008 A1
          HDH
        - Partyrock Crew - Basstown, 1989; SR-27217; Partyrock Crew (Box 58)
          Catalog # SH-1001-DJ; A-side Matrix # SH-1001-A
          Shatter Proof
          Miami, Florida
        - Pasadenas - Yours sincerely, 1992; SR-27218; Pasadenas (Box 58)
          Catalog # 471264 1; A-side Matrix # 01 471264 20 1A1
        - Passage - Passage, 1981; SR-27219; Passage (Box 58)
          Catalog # SP-4851; A-side Matrix # SPO-4851-A
        - Passport - Iguaçu, 1977; SR-27220; Passport (Box 58)
          Catalog # SD 36-149; A-side Matrix # ST-C-773803-A
          ATCO Records
        - Passport - Oceanliner, 1980; SR-27221; Passport (Box 59)
          Catalog # SD 19265; A-side Matrix # ST-A-804435-C SP
        - Pate, Johnny - Brother on the run (the original soundtrack), 1973; SR-27222; Pate, Johnny; Wade, Adam (Box 59)
          Catalog # PLP-45; A-side Matrix # PLP45A
          Perception Records
        - Paul, Leston - Soca invasion, 1985; SR-27223; Paul, Leston; New York Connection (Box 59)
          Catalog # BSR-LP-030; A-side Matrix # BSR-LP-030-A
          B's Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Paul Mac - Bateman Tower EP, 1997; SR-27224; Paul Mac (Box 59)
          Catalog # FMD 008; A-side Matrix # FMD 008- A1
          Fragmented Records
        - Paul Mauriat Plus - Overseas call, 1978; SR-25687; Paul Mauriat Plus (Box 59)
          Catalog # SRM-1-3746; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-3746 A-CT7 IT
          Mercury
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Paul, Simon - Drum.three.EP, 2000; SR-27225; Paul, Simon (Box 59)
          Catalog # FDCO-403; A-side Matrix # FDCO-403-A
          Fiction Design Company 416
          Canada
        - Peaches and Herb - Saying something, 1981; SR-27226; Peaches and Herb (Box 59)
          Catalog # PD-1-6332; A-side Matrix # PD 16332 AS PRCC1-1
          Polydor
        - Pedagogues - La femme, 1986; SR-27227; Pedagogues (Box 59)
          Catalog # 8385-3; A-side Matrix # RYTHMO 8385-3 A T1
          Rythmo-Disc
          Paris, France
        - Peebles, Ann - Tellin' it, 1975; SR-27228; Peebles, Ann (Box 59)
          Catalog # SHL 32091; A-side Matrix # SHL-689
          Hi Records
        - Pendergrasss, Teddy - It's time for love, 1981; SR-27229; Pendergrasss, Teddy (Box 59)
          Catalog # TZ 37491; A-side Matrix # PIR-AL-37491-2AJ
          Philadelphia International Records
        - Pendergrasss, Teddy - Where did all the lovin' go, 1979; SR-27230; Pendergrasss, Teddy (Box 59)
          Catalog # AS 739; A-side Matrix # XSS-167128-1A
        - Pendergrasss, Teddy - Teddy, 1979; SR-27231; Pendergrasss, Teddy (Box 59)
          Catalog # FZ 36003; A-side Matrix # PIR BL-36003-1H
        - People's Choice - People's Choice, 1980; SR-27232; People's Choice (Box 59)
          Catalog # NBLP 7246; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7246-ASK2
        - People's Choice - We got the rhythm, 1976; SR-27233; People's Choice (Box 59)
          Catalog # PZ 34124; A-side Matrix # TSOP-AL-34124-1B
          TSOP
        - Per Cussion - Manhattan jungle, 1986; SR-27234; Per Cussion (Box 59)
          Catalog # FOG 86001; A-side Matrix # 76-20158-012
          Fog Records
          Frankfurt, Germany
        - Per Cussion - Beatwave, 1985; SR-27235; Per Cussion (Box 59)
          Catalog # FROG 85002; A-side Matrix # 85002-B
        - Peraza, Armando - Wild thing, 1969; SR-27236; Peraza, Armando (Box 59)
          Catalog # SK5D; A-side Matrix # SK-5D-A
          Skye Records
        - Perigeo - Fata morgana, 1977; SR-27237; Perigeo (Box 59)
          Catalog # TPL1-1228; A-side Matrix # PL-1-1228
          RCA Victor
        - Perren, Freddie - Music from the soundtrack of Record City, 1977; SR-27238; Perren, Freddie; St. Lewis, Keni; Gadson, James; Diego, Fritz; Dees, Rick; Starbuck, Gary (Box 59)
          Catalog # PD-1-8002; A-side Matrix # PD-1-8002-AS-CP 1
        - Perry & Sanlin - We're the winners, 1981; SR-27264; Perry & Sanlin (Box 59)
          Catalog # ST-12180; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12180 Z2
          Capitol Records
        - Perry, James - April lady, 1981; SR-27239; Perry, James (Box 59)
          Catalog # CAR-802-D; A-side Matrix # CAR-5004-DK-2-A
          Carnival Records
        - Pet Shop Boys - Actually, 1987; SR-27265; Pet Shop Boys (Box 59)
          Catalog # PCSD 104; A-side Matrix # PCSD 104 A-4C-1-1-H
          Parlophone
        - Petite - Teens, 1986; SR-27266; Petite (Box 59)
          Catalog # YRC-786-23.1; A-side Matrix # YRC-786-23-1-A
          York's Records
        - Perry, Lee "Scratch" - Mystic miracle star, 1982; SR-27240; Perry, Lee "Scratch"; Majestics (Box 59)
          Catalog # HB06; A-side Matrix # ROU HBO6-A
          Heartbeat Records
          Sommerville, Massachussetts
        - Phase II Pan Groove - Rags, 1976; SR-27267; Phase II Pan Groove (Box 59)
          Catalog # S 010; A-side Matrix # CR S 010 A
          Charlie's Records
        - Vega, Luis - Phat kat traxxx, 1995; SR-27241; Vega, Luis (Box 59)
          In same jacket as # SR-27244. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CR-2019-EP; A-side Matrix # CR-2019-A PHAT
          Cutting Records
        - Vega, Luis - Phat kat traxxx, 1995; SR-27244; Vega, Luis (Box 59)
          In same jacket as # SR-27241. 2 copies.
        - Philadelphia Bluntz - Shakey shakey (Li'l bodies), 1996; SR-27242; Philadelphia Bluntz (Box 59)
          Catalog # ID049T; A-side Matrix # ID 049T B2
          Indochina
          London, United Kingdom
        - Philarmonics - For Elise (disco version); Piano concerto, 1978; SR-27243; Philarmonics (Box 59)
          Catalog # CPD-0003; A-side Matrix # AS-CPD-OO03-CP
          Capricorn Records
          Nashville, Tennesse
        - Phillinganes, Greg - Significant gains, 1981; SR-27245; Phillinganes, Greg (Box 59)
          In same jacket as # SR-27246. 2 copies.
          Catalog # P-17; A-side Matrix # P17-A-3-SP
          Planet Records
        - Phillinganes, Greg - Significant gains, 1981; SR-27246; Phillinganes, Greg (Box 59)
          In same jacket as # SR-27245. 2 copies.
        - Phillips, Esther - Our day will come, 1979; SR-27247; Phillips, Esther (Box 59)
          Catalog # MK-101; A-side Matrix # MK 101 A1
        - Philly Cream - Sly-hi, 1978; SR-27248; Philly Cream (Box 59)
          Catalog # D-113; A-side Matrix # D-113-A SP
          Fantasy WMOT Records
        - Phil 'n' The Blanks - Lands and peoples, 1982; SR-27249; Phil 'n' The Blanks (Box 59)
          Catalog # PRL-8-56; A-side Matrix # PRL-8-56 N-Z08071XA
          Pink Records
        - Photoglo - Photoglo, 1980; SR-27250; Photoglo (Box 59)
          Catalog # T-604; A-side Matrix # M-604-AS-A-1S
          20th Century Fox Records
        - Phreek - Patrick Adams presents Phreek, 1978; SR-27251; Phreek; Adams, Patrick (Box 59)
          Catalog # ST-A-784159-PR; A-side Matrix # ST-A-784159-A
        - Phunky Alien - Planet 2020 (Disc one), 1996; SR-27262; Phunky Alien; TC Islam (Box 59)
          In same jacket as # SR-27263. Double album.
          Catalog # ANTILP2; A-side Matrix # ANTILP002A
          Anti Static Recordings
        - Phunky Alien - Planet 2020 (Disc two), 1996; SR-27263; Phunky Alien; TC Islam (Box 59)
          In same jacket as # SR-27262. Double album.
          Catalog # ANTILP2; A-side Matrix # ANTILP002C
        - Pickett, Wilson - The best of Wilson Pickett, 1984; SR-27252; Pickett, Wilson (Box 59)
          Catalog # 81283-1-Y; A-side Matrix # ST A 855807 A 1-1
        - Pickett, Wilson - Right track, 1981; SR-27253; Pickett, Wilson (Box 59)
          Catalog # SW-17043; A-side Matrix # SW-1-170043-A-Z3
          EMI America
        - Pickett, Wilson - In Philadelphia, 1970; SR-27268; Pickett, Wilson (Box 59)
          Catalog # SD 8270; A-side Matrix # ST-A-701978-C
        - Pickett, Wilson - I want you, 1979; SR-27269; Pickett, Wilson (Box 59)
          Catalog # SW-17019; A-side Matrix # SW-17019 A
        - Pied Piper of Funkingham - I wanna play; Blow some funk this way, 1981; SR-27254; Pied Piper of Funkingham (Box 59)
          Catalog # C.C.120002; A-side Matrix # CC-120002
          Chocolate Cholly's
          Gastonia, North Carolina
        - Pigbag - Getting up, 1982; SR-27255; Pigbag (Box 59)
          Catalog # TEES 1213; A-side Matrix # TEES-12-13A-1A
          Stiff Records
        - Pigforce - 9ine MM, 1997; SR-27256; Pigforce (Box 59)
          Catalog # 12 BRW 349; A-side Matrix # 12 BRW 349 A
          4th & Broadway
        - Pine, Courtney - Underground (disc one), 1997; SR-27257; Pine, Courtney (Box 59)
          In same jacket as # SR-27258. Double album.
          Catalog # 537 745-1; A-side Matrix # 539 279-1-A
          Polygram Records
        - Pine, Courtney - Underground (disc two), 1997; SR-27258; Pine, Courtney (Box 59)
          In same jacket as # SR-27257. Double album.
          Catalog # 537 745-1; A-side Matrix # 539 279-1-C
        - Pink Flyod - The wall (disc one), 1979; SR-27259; Pink Flyod (Box 59)
          In same jacket as # SR-27260. Double album.
          Catalog # PC2 36183; A-side Matrix # PAL 36184-1D
        - Pink Flyod - The wall (disc two), 1979; SR-27260; Pink Flyod (Box 59)
          In same jacket as # SR-27259. Double album.
          Catalog # PC2 36183; A-side Matrix # PAL 36185-1BC
        - Pioneers - Feel the rhythm, 1976; SR-27261; Pioneers (Box 59)
          Catalog # 9286 172; A-side Matrix # 9286 172
        - Planets - Planets, 1980; SR-27270; Planets (Box 59)
          Catalog # M7-934R1; A-side Matrix # M7-934R1-A-13A
          Motown
        - Plasmatics - Beyond the valley of 1984, 1981; SR-27271; Plasmatics (Box 59)
          Catalog # WOW II; A-side Matrix # WOW II A-1A
          Stiff America
        - Plastics - Plastics, 1981; SR-27272; Plastics (Box 59)
          Catalog # ILPS 9627; A-side Matrix # ILPS 1 9627 LW2
          Island Records
        - Play By Numbers - Cloud nine, 1983; SR-27273; Play By Numbers (Box 60)
          Catalog # 27-003; A-side Matrix # 27-003-A
          Ice Water Records
        - Players Association - The things you get me to do, 1981; SR-27274; Players Association (Box 60)
          Catalog # SPV 49; A-side Matrix # SPV 49-A-1B
          Vanguard Disco
        - Platypus - Platypus, 1979; SR-27275; Platypus (Box 60)
          Catalog # NBLP 7171 AS; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7171-K-AS
        - Playmate - Love dance, 1978; SR-27276; Playmate (Box 60)
          Catalog # SG 218; A-side Matrix # SG-218-A
          Salsoul Records
        - Pleasure - Glide, 1979; SR-27277; Pleasure (Box 60)
          Catalog # D-146; A-side Matrix # D 146 AS-1D
          Fantasy Records
        - Pleasure - Future now, 1979; SR-27278; Pleasure (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27279. 2 copies.
          Catalog # F-9578; A-side Matrix # F-9578A-1B-RE-2
        - Pleasure - Future now, 1979; SR-27279; Pleasure (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27278. 2 copies.
          Catalog # F-9578; A-side Matrix # F-9578A-RE-1C
        - Plump DJs - Electric disco; Plumpy chunks, 1999; SR-27280; Plump DJs (Box 60)
          Catalog # FLR.013; A-side Matrix # 1B1 FLR 013
          Finger Lickin' Records
        - Plump DJs - In stereo; Squeaks & bleeps, 2003; SR-27281; Plump DJs (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27282. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FLR 038; A-side Matrix # FLR 038-A
        - Plump DJs - In stereo; Squeaks & bleeps, 2003; SR-27282; Plump DJs (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27281. 2 copies.
        - Plump DJs - Eargasm (disc one), 2003; SR-27283; Plump DJs (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27284. Double album.
          Catalog # FLRLP007; A-side Matrix # FLR LP 007 A
        - Plump DJs - Eargasm (disc two), 2003; SR-27284; Plump DJs (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27283. Double album.
          Catalog # FLRLP007; A-side Matrix # FLR LP 007 C
        - Plump DJs - The funk hits the fan; The gate, 2003; SR-27285; Plump DJs (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27286. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FLR41; A-side Matrix # 08 51481 20 1A1 FLR 041
        - Plump DJs - The funk hits the fan; The gate, 2003; SR-27286; Plump DJs (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27285. 2 copies.
        - Plump DJs - The push; Remember my name, 2000; SR-27287; Plump DJs (Box 60)
          Catalog # FLR.016; A-side Matrix # 08 42538 20 1A1 FLR 016
        - Pockets - So delicious, 1979; SR-27288; Pockets (Box 60)
          Catalog # JC 36001; A-side Matrix # PAL 36001-2G
          ARC
        - Pointer, Bonnie - Bonnie Pointer, 1979; SR-27289; Pointer, Bonnie (Box 60)
          Catalog # M7-929 R1; A-side Matrix # M 7929 R1-SA-18B 13B
        - Pointer, Noel - All my reasons, 1981; SR-27290; Pointer, Noel (Box 60)
          Catalog # LT-1094; A-side Matrix # LT-1-1094-Z LAP-1
          Liberty
        - Pointer Sisters - Black and white, 1981; SR-27291; Pointer Sisters (Box 60)
          Catalog # P-18; A-side Matrix # P-18-A-SP
        - Pointer Sisters - Break out, 1983; SR-27292; Pointer Sisters (Box 60)
          Catalog # BXL1-4705; A-side Matrix # BXL1-4705-A-115
        - Police - Reggata de blanc, 1979; SR-27293; Police (Box 60)
          Catalog # SP-4792; A-side Matrix # T1 A&M SP 4792-A-T3
        - Police - Reggata de blanc, 1979; SR-27294; Police (Box 60)
          Catalog # SP-4792; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 04792A RCA 1
        - Police - Ghost in the machine, 1981; SR-27295; Police (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27296. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-3730; A-side Matrix # SP0 3730 A CP2
        - Police - One world (not three); Too much information, 1981; SR-27296; Police (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27295. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-17173; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 017173 A S1
        - Polyrock - Changing hearts, 1981; SR-27297; Polyrock (Box 60)
          Catalog # AFL1-4043; A-side Matrix # AFL1-4043A-1
        - Pompey, Ron - Banana police, 1988; SR-27298; Pompey, Ron (Box 60)
          Catalog # GS 2291; A-side Matrix # GS 2291-A
          Straker's Records
        - Ponderosa Twins Plus One - 2+2+1= Ponderosa Twins Plus One, 1971; SR-27299; Ponderosa Twins Plus One (Box 60)
          Catalog # H-5001; A-side Matrix # ALL PLATINUM H-2000